And in this segment, I'm just going to explain a little bit how we're going to wrap up our mural.
We're doing a construction sign here and it's going to say--we're going to put another put coat on it so it's a solid orange like a real construction sign.
And then we're going to put "Caution: Boys at Work" and we'll do that in black writing so it looks like one.
And then I've taped it off right here so when I paint in my post, for this to be in the foreground, then it looks like it's standing on a post in the foreground and then you've got the construction in the background.
After we're done with that, I'm just going to put in a little bit of shadows on the bottom.
You can use a stencil to put in your lettering if you ever do lettering.
I like to hand-paint my mine in.
I'll usually ruler it out and tape it in line so your words are really straight on there, but stencils work too.
And what I would do is I would do another coat on this, let it dry, and then I would pencil in my letters so I get it right with my paint.
So as soon as I get my letters painted in, then I can or--I'm sorry--draw in with a pencil then I can paint it in.